{
    "subject": "resource/Al_Murray",
    "predicate": "ontology/genre",
    "object": "resource/Political_satire",
    "human_readable": "Al Murray's genre is Political satire.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8672181367874146,
            "question": "What makes Al Murray's political satire unique?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.772534191608429,
            "question": "Why do you think people enjoy Al Murray's political satire?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5671709775924683,
            "question": "What topics does Al Murray often satirize in his work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45072370767593384,
            "question": "What genre of comedy is Al Murray known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4003845155239105,
            "question": "Who is Al Murray's target audience?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25756189227104187,
            "question": "Can you give an example of a common theme in Al Murray's comedic material?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22566835582256317,
            "question": "Does Al Murray's comedy typically aim to be informative or entertaining?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21013391017913818,
            "question": "What are some of the key elements that contribute to Al Murray's comedic success?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20965947210788727,
            "question": "What type of humor does Al Murray use in his performances?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17055140435695648,
            "question": "How would you describe the overall tone of Al Murray's comedy?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Al Murray's genre is Political satire.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8631_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of humor does Al Murray use in his performances?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8631_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of the key elements that contribute to Al Murray's comedic success?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8631_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Al Murray's comedy typically aim to be informative or entertaining?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8631_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8631_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8631_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8631_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8631_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8631_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8631_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8631_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8631_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8631_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8631_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents indicate that Al Murray is known for his unique brand of hard-edged social and political satire, which supports the statement that his genre includes political satire."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}